20, 22, PSY coming back
(이리 오너라)
Long time no see, huh? 오래간만이지 huh?
우리 다시 웃고, 울고, 지지고, 볶고
Let's get loco
Pandemic's over, uh 그래, 기분이 오져 uh
다시 그분이 오죠 uh
Everybody say
뻑쩍지근해, 껄쩍지근해
시끌벅적거리네 너무 좋아 북적거리네
동서남북, 강남강북
싹 다 모여 throw your hands in the air
I say yeah!
Can you feel it?
Whoa yeah
Whoa
Can you feel it?
Oh yeah
준비하시고, 쏘세요
That that I like that
기분 좋아 baby
흔들어 좌우, 위, 아래로
One, two, three, to the four
That that I like that
That that I like that, baby
It's like that, that you
That that I like that
That that I like that, baby
It's like that
야, 내가 뭐 하는 사람인지 까먹었지?
That that I like that
Like that
시간이 지나도 변함없이
That that I like that
Like that
I don't care, I don't care
That I like that
That that I like that
Like that
내가 바라보고 바래왔던 사람들아 모두 다 ready, set, go
되려 늘어난 맷집,
때리던 분이 불편하겠지
너네 바램대로 망할거라 고사 지낸 사람들을 모아다가 가볍게 때찌
적당히 하라고 oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh
그냥 닥치고 다 같이 놀아보자고
민윤기와 박재상
Can you feel it?
Whoa yeah
Whoa
Can you feel it?
Oh yeah
준비하시고
쏘세요
That that I like that
기분 좋아, baby
흔들어 좌우, 위, 아래로
One, two, three
To the four
That that I like that
That that I like that, baby
It's like that, that's right
That that I like that
That that I like that, baby
It's like that, that's right
That that I like that
Do what you want
Say what you want
Say what?
That that I like that, baby
Do what you want
Say what you want
Say what?
That that I like that, baby
That that I like that